Micaela G. Signorelli

139 Alderson Road. Sheffield, United Kingdom S2 4UE

07 - 871204888 - m.signorelli@gmail.com - Date of Birth: 15/05/1990 - Italian - http://www.micaelasignorelli.com

Artist, Scholar, Teacher, Translator and Carer. Management experience in Cultural. Proactive Worker and Manager with focus on research, strategy, problem solving and work ethics. Passionate about producing Cultural events in deprived areas. Sales experience of 10 years.

Education

- Master of Arts in Theatre and Performance Studies, *University of Sheffield*, Sheffield, UK. Sept 2015-2016.
- Course in Transmedia Storytelling, Sungkyunkwan University (SKKU), Seoul, South Korea (Distance Learning). Dec 2017 Jan 2018.
- Bachelor of Arts, Degree in Theatre Pontifical Catholic University of Chile, Santiago,
 Chile. March 2009 Dec 2014
- Minor in Developmental Psychology, Pontifical Catholic University of Chile, Santiago, Chile. March 2010 June 2014
- Middle and High School, Andrée English School, Santiago, Chile. 1995-2008.

Work Experience

- Support Care Worker. Abbeycare. Sheffield, United Kingdom. Oct 2017 to present.
- Face to Face interpreter: Spanish, Language Line Solutions, Sheffield, United Kingdom, Sept 2016 to present.
- Telesales Executive: International Team. Ant Marketing, Sheffield, United Kingdom, Nov 2016 to Oct 2017.
- Production Management Assistant, La Memoria Museum of Human Rights, Santiago, Chile. July 2015 to September 2015. Production area of the Theatre Cycle at the Museum and attention of public
- Workshop Manager, San Antonio Cultural Center, Illustrious Municipality of San Antonio. San Antonio, V Región. August 2014 to August 2015.
 Managing and coordinating the development of Creative Workshops and cultural activities for general public and numerous Minor Protection State Agencies. Institutional voice for Cultural Center publicity.
- Director, Playwright, Co Researcher Contrasujeto Theatre Company. Santiago. July 2014 to July 2015. Stage research in three stages. Analysis of the impact of personal identity.
- Actress and Model, Freelance. Santiago, Chile. Sheffield, United Kingdom. January 2010 to present. Stage acting, writing and producing. Short and long films, TV, radio and photo shoots.
- Make-up Artist, Freelance. Santiago, Chile. Sheffield, United Kingdom. January 2010 to present. Fantasy and everyday stage and event make-up.
- **Photographer**, Freelance. Santiago, Chile. Sheffield, United Kingdom. January 2010 to present. Artistic photography, events and book portraits.

Teaching experience

- **Spanish Teacher**, Private. 2016 to Present.
- **Assistant Professor**, Pontifical Catholic University of Chile. Santiago, Chile. August 2013 December 2014. Paradigms of the Arts Course. To Dr. Andrea Pelegrí Kristic.

Languages

- English, IELTS, 8.0. British Council. Oct 2014. FCE, A, Cambridge University, Dec 2007.
- German, A2, The University of Sheffield 2016.
- Italian, Stadio Italiano of Santiago. December 2006.
- Mandarin Chinese Beginner. Confucius Institute, The University of Sheffield.
- Spanish. Native language.

Software

HTML 5.1 - Basic Python - Basic Php - Microsoft Office - Apple iMovie - Mad Mapper - Adobe Photoshop - Audacity